forttroff.com 2016-11-19

# Fort Troff: Terms of Use + Privacy Policy

When you make a purchase from Fort Troff, you provide us with personal information such as your name, address, phone number, credit card information, and email address. We keep a record of this information which is covered by our privacy policy and is held in the strictest of confidence. All information submitted via our website is secure and private. Your entire transaction with Fort Troff is completely private. We do not and will not ever sell, rent or grant access to our customer records to any other company or person for any reason, except when required by law. 

## Your Information Is Never Shared

When you place an order with Fort Troff, we ask you to provide us with various types of information. These are used to verify credit card ownership and process your order. We do not sell your information to any third parties. 

## Name and Billing Address

This information is collected in order to verify that the person placing the order is the person who owns the credit card. We do not send out marketing materials via postal mail, and you will never receive anything at this address unless it is also your shipping address where you would like to send your order. 

## Shipping Address

Your order will arrive at this address. It can be the same as your billing address. 

## Email Address 

Your email address is used to send order-related emails such as order updates and confirmations, online shipping confirmations, and customer service inquiries. You also have the option to join the Fort Troff email list, or you may choose to opt-out. 

## Phone Number

We ship via UPS which requires a recipient contact number. You may be contacted by phone in case we need to reach you about your order in the event that there is a delay in manufacturing or shipping your order. Additionally, our customers do not always have access to email, and a phone number is used as an alternate method of communication. When it is necessary to contact our customers regarding their order, we try to provide email correspondence as often as possible. However, on occasion, phone contact is the easiest method. We will not solicit you or call for any reason other than in regards to your order. 

## Age

We ask you to confirm that you are 21 or older to order products from our website. We do not sell our products to minors. 

## Discrete Packaging

We ship all of our packages in nondescript brown cardboard boxes that are sealed with reinforced camouflage tape. The return address on the label is listed as F.T., and there is no indication of the contents of the package. Your privacy is our utmost concern. 

## Billing

Any charge from Fort Troff will appear as "F.T." on your bank/credit card statement to protect your privacy. 

## Opt-Out

When you make a purchase with Fort Troff, you are required to provide your email address. This allows us to contact you with order updates and confirmations, online shipping confirmations, and customer service inquiries. On the order form you will notice the option to be added to the pig army email list is automatically selected. The Fort Troff emails provide you with information on sales, special offers, weekly promotional events, exclusive email discounts, and new products for sale. To opt-out of the Fort Troff email list, simply uncheck the box. If you do elect to subscribe to our email list, please know that it is 100% US CAN-Spam compliant and you may unsubscribe or change your subscription preferences at any time. The Fort Troff email list only uses your email address and does not store your name or any of your other personal information. 

## Security

We use only the highest level of security for your personal data, which includes the industry standard 128-bit SSL encryption. When you purchase from Fort Troff, you can be assured that your information is very secure.
